Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪I plant miles of peach blossoms just for her♪
أزرع أميالاً من أزهار الخوخ خصيصاً من أجلها
♪Sweet words bloom upon those branches♪
♪تزهر الكلمات العذبة على تلك الأغصان♪
♪Love runs deep, trapped in longing♪
♪الحب عميق، محاصر في الشوق♪
♪Night listens answers to longing are the most terrifying♪
♪تستمع الليل إلى إجابات الشوق، وهي الأكثر رعباً♪
♪At my fingertips, worries drift and linger♪
♪على أطراف أصابعي، تتلاشى الهموم وتستمر♪
♪Having tasted a moment of carefree joy♪
♪ بعد أن تذوقت لحظة من الفرح الخالي من الهموم ♪
♪Today, I pluck romance and moonlight♪
اليوم، أقطف الرومانسية وضوء القمر
♪And weave them all into a painting♪
♪ واجمعها كلها في لوحة ♪
=The Ultimate Vow, Unknown to You=
=العهد الأسمى، الذي تجهله=
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
I will uncover the truth and avenge you with my own hands.
سأكشف الحقيقة وأنتقم لك بيدي.
Kill!
قتل!
Find the right moment,
ابحث عن اللحظة المناسبة،
then leave first.
ثم ارحل أولاً.
Careful.
انتبه.
Yuwen Que.
يوين كيو.
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
General, you carry quite the air.
يا جنرال، أنت تتمتع بهيبة كبيرة.
Do you want the military seal, or your life?
هل تريد الحصول على الختم العسكري، أم حياتك؟
General, you would do well to think carefully.
أيها الجنرال، من الأفضل لك أن تفكر ملياً.
You...
أنت...
General, you must not.
أيها الجنرال، لا يجوز لك ذلك.
If you dare harm her in the slightest,
إذا تجرأت على إيذائها ولو قليلاً،
I will make sure you suffer a fate worse than death.
سأضمن أن تعاني مصيراً أسوأ من الموت.
That depends on the General's choice.
هذا يعتمد على اختيار الجنرال.
I will give you three days.
سأمنحك ثلاثة أيام.
(Joy)
(مرح)
So it was Your Highness who laid this perfect trap.
إذن، كان صاحب السمو هو من نصب هذا الفخ المحكم.
You should have known long ago,
كان ينبغي عليك أن تعرف ذلك منذ زمن بعيد.
I would never allow you to marry him.
لن أسمح لكِ بالزواج منه أبداً.
A prince of Mobei,
أمير موبي،
reduced to the ways of bandits,
انحطوا إلى أساليب قطاع الطرق،
seizing another man's wife by force.
الاستيلاء على زوجة رجل آخر بالقوة.
Your Highness shows such disregard for decorum.
يُظهر سموكم استهتاراً كبيراً باللياقة.
The face of the Mobei royal family
وجه العائلة المالكة في موبي
has been utterly ruined by you.
لقد دمرتها أنت تماماً.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
I care about any of that?
هل أهتم بأي من ذلك؟
You are insane.
أنت مجنون.
Yes.
نعم.
I am insane.
أنا مجنون.
Watching you marry another,
أشاهدك تتزوجين من آخر،
how could I not go mad?
كيف لي ألا أجن؟
You lost the right to say such things long ago.
لقد فقدت الحق في قول مثل هذه الأشياء منذ زمن بعيد.
The moment you raised your blade and struck,
في اللحظة التي رفعت فيها نصل سيفك وضربت،
you should have known this day would come.
كان ينبغي عليك أن تعلم أن هذا اليوم سيأتي.
Hate me if you wish.
اكرهني إن شئت.
Kill me if you must.
اقتلني إن كان لا بد من ذلك.
I accept it.
أقبل ذلك.
But this time,
لكن هذه المرة،
I will never let you escape.
لن أدعك تهرب أبداً.
Do you know how disgusting
هل تعلم كم هو مقرف؟
you look right now?
كيف تبدو الآن؟
♪In the end, it becomes an epitaph♪
♪في النهاية، يصبح نقشاً على شاهد قبر♪
You and I crossed that line long ago.
لقد تجاوزنا أنا وأنت ذلك الخط منذ زمن بعيد.
We should have stood together before the altar.
كان ينبغي أن نقف معاً أمام المذبح.
It was Su Changji
كان سو تشانغجي
who tore you away from me!
من الذي انتزعك مني!
Whatever bound us ended long ago.
مهما كان ما يربطنا فقد انتهى منذ زمن بعيد.
Let go of me.
اتركني وشأني.
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقاً
this bit of pain will make me release you?
هل سيدفعني هذا الألم البسيط إلى إطلاق سراحك؟
Go on, bite.
هيا، عض.
That is the Ru I remember.
هذه هي رو التي أتذكرها.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
His Majesty summons you to the Imperial Study.
يستدعيكم جلالته إلى المكتب الإمبراطوري.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
We will finish this when I return.
سننهي هذا الأمر عندما أعود.
Yuwen Que.
يوين كيو.
You will die without mercy.
ستموت بلا رحمة.
Then we go to hell together.
ثم نذهب إلى الجحيم معاً.
Watch her carefully.
راقبها جيداً.
Do not let her
لا تدعها
hurt herself.
أصابت نفسها.
Yes.
نعم.
I swear,
أقسم،
you will pay
ستدفع
for everything you did today.
شكراً لك على كل ما فعلته اليوم.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
This is a treasured relic from Mobei Changlong.
هذه قطعة أثرية ثمينة من موبي تشانغلونغ.
It is said that whoever possesses this tortoise shell
يقال إن من يمتلك صدفة السلحفاة هذه
will be blessed with great fortune over the realm.
سينعمون بحظٍ عظيم في المملكة.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
It is indeed a rare piece.
إنها قطعة نادرة بالفعل.
Wen Ling, you have put real thought into this.
وين لينغ، لقد فكرتِ في هذا الأمر ملياً.
Your Majesty, I pay my respects.
جلالة الملك، أقدم احترامي.
Your behavior last night in my Imperial Garden was reckless.
كان سلوكك الليلة الماضية في حديقتي الإمبراطورية متهوراً.
Do not think it escaped me.
لا تظن أن الأمر غاب عني.
I accept my fault.
أتحمل مسؤولية خطئي.
Que.
ماذا.
Wen Ling
ون لينغ
gentle in nature, and proper in conduct.
لطيف في طبيعته، وحسن سلوكه.
I have already granted your marriage.
لقد وافقتُ بالفعل على زواجكما.
Father.
أب.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Do you still dare to object?
هل ما زلت تجرؤ على الاعتراض؟
I beg Father to revoke the decree.
أرجو من أبي أن يلغي هذا القرار.
I would rather die than comply.
أفضّل الموت على الامتثال.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I have already given my heart.
لقد وهبتُ قلبي بالفعل.
I will never betray her.
لن أخونها أبداً.
Insolent!
وقح!
Do you know how many merits Wen Ling's father
هل تعلم كم عدد مزايا والد وين لينغ؟
has rendered to the court?
هل قدم إلى المحكمة؟
From now on, Que will be under your discipline.
من الآن فصاعدًا، سيكون كيو تحت إشرافك.
I admit my guilt.
أعترف بذنبي.
But this matter cannot be.
لكن هذا الأمر لا يمكن أن يكون كذلك.
You!
أنت!
I beg Father's forgiveness.
أرجو من أبي أن يغفر لي.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Please return.
يرجى العودة.
I have waited for you all these years.
لقد انتظرتك طوال هذه السنوات.
Do you truly not know how I feel?
ألا تعرف حقاً ما أشعر به؟
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
there is room in my heart for only one person.
لا يوجد في قلبي متسع إلا لشخص واحد.
Your Highness, Young Lady Shen asked me for joss paper.
صاحبة السمو، طلبت مني الشابة شين ورقًا للزينة.
She said today
قالت اليوم
marks the death anniversary of her closest kin.
يصادف هذا اليوم ذكرى وفاة أقرب أقربائها.
Mother.
الأم.
Before you passed,
قبل رحيلك،
you said all men in this world are fickle.
قلتَ إن جميع الرجال في هذا العالم متقلبون.
Yet I refused to believe it.
لكنني رفضت تصديق ذلك.
Now it seems,
والآن يبدو،
how bitterly ironic.
يا لها من مفارقة مريرة!
He swore to protect me for a lifetime,
أقسم أن يحميني طوال حياتي،
to grow old with me, side by side.
أن نكبر معاً، جنباً إلى جنب.
Yet in the end,
لكن في النهاية،
I merely invited a wolf into my home,
لقد دعوت ذئباً إلى منزلي فحسب،
and with his own hands, he destroyed my entire family.
وبيديه، دمر عائلتي بأكملها.
That night,
في تلك الليلة،
I saw you collapse in a pool of blood.
رأيتك تنهار في بركة من الدماء.
Mother.
الأم.
Qingru.
كينغرو.
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
you must live on, and live well.
يجب أن تستمر في الحياة، وأن تعيش حياة طيبة.
No.
لا.
This jade pendant
قلادة من اليشم
will keep you safe.
سيحافظ على سلامتك.
Mother.
الأم.
I am utterly useless.
أنا عديم الفائدة تماماً.
I let you die such a cruel death.
لقد تركتك تموت ميتة قاسية.
My greatest fault
أكبر خطأ ارتكبته
was believing a heartless man.
كنت أصدق رجلاً عديم الرحمة.
I destroyed an entire family.
لقد دمرت عائلة بأكملها.
Heng Dao.
هنغ داو.
Go investigate for me
اذهب وابحث لي
who killed Ru's family.
من قتل عائلة رو؟
Yes.
نعم.
(Ru,)
(رو،)
(I deserve)
(أنا أستحق)
(your hatred.)
(كراهيتك.)
(But the truth of that night)
(لكن حقيقة تلك الليلة)
(will one day)
(سيحدث ذلك يوماً ما)
(come to light.)
(تتضح الأمور.)
♪I plant miles of peach blossoms just for her♪
أزرع أميالاً من أزهار الخوخ خصيصاً من أجلها
♪Sweet words bloom upon those branches♪
♪تزهر الكلمات العذبة على تلك الأغصان♪
♪Love runs deep, trapped in longing♪
♪الحب عميق، محاصر في الشوق♪
♪Night listens answers to longing are the most terrifying♪
♪تستمع الليل إلى إجابات الشوق، وهي الأكثر رعباً♪
♪At my fingertips, worries drift and linger♪
♪على أطراف أصابعي، تتلاشى الهموم وتستمر♪
♪Having tasted a moment of carefree joy♪
♪ بعد أن تذوقت لحظة من الفرح الخالي من الهموم ♪
♪Today, I pluck romance and moonlight♪
اليوم، أقطف الرومانسية وضوء القمر
♪And weave them all into a painting♪
♪ واجمعها كلها في لوحة ♪
How could this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
It is you.
أنت هو.
What?
ماذا؟
So surprised, Your Highness?
متفاجئ جداً يا صاحب السمو؟
I see now.
فهمت الآن.
No wonder His Highness
لا عجب في ذلك يا صاحب السمو
defied the imperial decree today.
تحدوا المرسوم الإمبراطوري اليوم.
It was all for a woman like you.
كان كل ذلك من أجل امرأة مثلك.
Your Ladyship need not speak so harshly.
لا داعي لأن تتحدث سيدتي بهذه القسوة.
Do you know how long I waited for him?
هل تعلم كم انتظرته؟
Ten years.
عشر سنوات.
A full ten years.
عشر سنوات كاملة.
And what does ten years amount to?
وماذا تعني عشر سنوات؟
You dare insult me.
أتجرؤ على إهانتي؟
Look at where you stand now.
انظر إلى وضعك الحالي.
You are nothing more than His Highness's prisoner.
أنت لست سوى أسير لدى صاحب السمو.
A prisoner.
سجين.
At least I am not someone
على الأقل أنا لست شخصًا ما
willing to live forever in another's shadow.
مستعد للعيش إلى الأبد في ظل الآخرين.
You...
أنت...